

CONTACT

9361332589

iananisingaravelu97@gmail.com

② Coimbatore, Tamil Nadu, India

EDUCATION

BHARATHIAR UNIVERSITY

2019 – 2022 Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

KARPAGAM POLYTECHNIC COLLEGE

2012 – 2015 Diploma in Electronics and Communication

SKILLS

- Figma
- Adobe XD
- Typography
- Wireframing and Prototyping
- Responsive Design
- Creativity
- Leader
- Communication

Janani Singaravelu

UI/UX Designer

PROFILE

Highly motivated and professional Operations
Associate with over 7 years of experience providing
high-level support to the team. Organized and
dependable candidate successful at managing multiple
priorities with a positive attitude. Willingness to take
an added responsibilities to meet team goals. Skilled in
working under pressure and adapting to new
situations.

WORK EXPERIENCE

HC & INSURANCE OPERATIONS ASSOCIATE

NTT Data Services

2020 - Present

- Performed visual assessment of products to evaluate conformance with quality standards.
 Collaborated with a team to define business requirements for organizational processes, achieve productivity standards and adhere to accuracy standards.
- Assigned tasks, reviewed performance and devised improvement plans or corrections

SENIOR REPRESENTATIVE

NTT Data Services

2016 - 2020

- Strong verbal and written communication skills, with the ability to interact confidently with customers and colleagues.
- Skilled in analyzing complex problems and finding practical solutions.
- Ability to handle a dynamic and fast-paced work environment while adjusting to changing priorities and tasks.